dilos.com 2012-12-31

# Dilos.com Privacy Policy : Dilos Holiday World

|  PRIVACY POLICY    
---  
  
Understanding your concerns over online purchases, we would like to assure you that it is our priority to ensure security over the transactions and confidentiality over your personal data. We hereby set out the basic principles of our privacy policy. Should you still have any concerns, you are encouraged to ask for clarifications. None of this information (your personal data) is either sold or leased by us to any third party. 

**What we collect**

We collect information that you provide us at your own will, and such information does not usually go beyond the information that would be required for a direct booking with any hotel (i.e. name, full address, telephone, e-mail). Information is used by us in order to match each booking request with an individual, pass all necessary information to the hotel booked, issue an appropriate invoice and voucher, and secure payment of our services.

**What we do with the information**

Other than for booking purposes, we may ask for such information in some of our pages for the purchase of other services provided or for research/marketing, communication, membership or other purposes. In case you do not wish to be included in such mailing lists, if any, you have the option not to subscribe or to unsubscribe in case of an error or in case you change your mind.

We may also use this information to contact you before or when on a trip in order to inform you on serious events.

Furthermore, when you visit our site, we may collect statistical information about your visit. This information, which does not contain any personal data, will be used in order to evaluate and improve our site and services. Information to be kept is number of visits, visitors IP, pages visited, keywords used for searches etc. 

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a piece of information that our Website sends to your browser, which then stores this information on your system. When cookies are used, the website will be able to "remember" information about you and your preferences either until you exit your current browser window (if the cookie is temporary) or until you disable or delete the cookie.

Keep in mind that cookies contain no more information than you volunteer, and they are not able to "invade" your hard drive and return to the sender personal or other information from your computer.

Use of cookies will help you browse our site and us in order to allow our software to determine which page will be shown when you hit the back button in your browser. If you reach our site through one of our business partners, our web server may also send your browser a temporary cookie that reflects an "origination code" for that business partner. We use this information for statistical and marketing purposes. Cookies can also be used in order to help you fill in the forms available in our site and/or revisiting it.

**Bookings on behalf of Third Parties**

In cases where an individual proceeds with bookings on behalf of a third party, we assume that this person has obtained the necessary approval from the third party, and therefore we assume no liability for any unauthorized use of personal data by that person.

**Billing Information**

When the preferred way of payment is via credit card, then further to the abovementioned information we will collect all necessary details of the credit card used for the transaction in accordance with applicable legislation. Any information collected by us on the credit cards used, will not be further processed and in no case will it be forwarded to any of our suppliers or collaborators.

**Miscellaneous Information**

Some information may be collected automatically by us or by third parties every time you visit our website (e.g. cookies and computer information). Such information does not contain any personal information.

**Our obligations**

In cases we are required by law or when our interests are in jeopardy, we shall disclose all information requested.

**Miscellaneous**

We reserve the right to amend this policy when we deem necessary. In case of a material change of policy and for your protection, the privacy policy to be applied for you will be the one valid at the time of your transaction.

**Contacting**

For any inquiries you might have concerning our policy, you can get further info by contacting us at **info@dilos.com**.

**Security**

Security is a top priority at dilos.com. To safeguard your personal information, our systems are equipped with multiple security precautions throughout the booking process, and long after you have completed your transaction.

Our systems are protected by Digital Signatures for authentication and integrity, Certification Authority (thwate) that uniquely identifies the merchant, Secure Socket Layers (SSL) to ensure privacy and authentication, firewalls that act as shields to our computer networks from attack by viruses and hackers. Within those systems, sensitive information is encrypted to protect your personal data, like credit card numbers.

Our secure server software encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card information. The process of encryption takes the information you enter and converts it into bits of code that are securely transmitted over the Internet. This scrambled data cannot be read while travelling over the Internet.  
  
Hotels in these countries:
